Pelke, Bill; Papers apap205
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- General Activism, 1984-2000, Undated; 6; 5.08 cubic feet
  - Death Penalty Focus of California -The Sentry, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 32)
  - Death Penalty Focus of California -The Sentry, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 33)
  - Death Penalty Focus of California -The Sentry, 2000 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 34)
  - Death Penalty Information Center, 1992-1994; 1996-1997; Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 35)
  - Death Penalty Information Center - reports, 1992-1994; 1996 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 36)
  - The Death Row Forum, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 37)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 38)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 39)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1995 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 40)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1995 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 41)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1995 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 42)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1996 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 43)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1996 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 44)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1996 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 45)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1996 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 46)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 47)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 48)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 49)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 50)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 51)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1999 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 52)
  - Death Row's Lamp, 1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 53)
  - Dismas of Michiana, 1994-1995; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 54)
  - Dismas News, 1993-1995; 1997-1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 55)
  - Double Justice: Race and Capital Punishment, 1993 (Oversize 9, Vhs 3)
  - Emerging Summit to Strategize for the Abolition of the Death Penalty, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 56)
  - Endeavor: Live Voices from Death Row Across the U.S.A., 1990-1991 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 57)
  - Endeavor: Live Voices from Death Row Across the U.S.A., 1993 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 58)
  - Endeavor: Live Voices from Death Row Across the U.S.A., 1994-1996 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 59)
  - Endeavor Project, 1992; Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 60)
  - Envisioning a World Without Violence Conference, Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 61)
  - Execute Justice Not People - Button, Undated (Oversize 5, Item 12)
  - Fifth Avenue Foundation, 1994-196; Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 62)
  - Florida Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1991-1993; 1997; Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 63)
  - Forgiveness Institute, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 64)
  - Free Carl Napier - Bumper Sticker, Undated (Oversize 5, Item 65)
  - Friends Committee to Abolish the Death Penalty -The Quaker Abolitionist, 1996 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 66)
  - Friends Committee to Abolish the Death Penalty -The Quaker Abolitionist, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 67)
  - Friends Committee to Abolish the Death Penalty -The Quaker Abolitionist, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 68)
  - Friends Committee to Abolish the Death Penalty -The Quaker Abolitionist, 1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 69)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1993 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 70)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1993 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 71)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 72)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 73)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 74)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 75)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1995 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 76)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1995 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 77)
  - From Blues to Blessings Ministries, Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 78)
  - Fund for Life News and Notes, 1995 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 79)
  - Gary Graham Justice Coalition, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 80)
  - The Gathering, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 81)
  - The Gathering, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 82)
  - The Gathering, 1995 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 83)
  - GEM Ministries, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 84)
  - Generation Action, 1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 85)
  - Graterfriends, 1992 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 86)
  - Graterfriends, 1992 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 87)
  - Graterfriends, 1993 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 88)
  - Graterfriends, 1993 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 89)
  - Graterfriends, 1993 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 90)
  - Graterfriends, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 91)
  - Graterfriends, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 92)
  - Graterfriends, 1995 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 93)
  - Graterfriends, 1995 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 94)
  - Graterfriends, 1995 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 95)
  - Graterfriends, 1996 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 96)
  - Graterfriends, 1996 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 97)
  - Graterfriends, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 98)
  - Graterfriends, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 99)
  - Graterfriends, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 100)
  - Graterfriends, 1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 101)
  - Graterfriends, 1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 102)
  - Graterfriends, 1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 103)
  - Graterfriends, 1999 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 104)
  - Graterfriends, 1999 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 105)
  - Hansen House of Hospitality and Criminal Justice Ministries -Bars and Stripes, 1990; 1992 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 106)
  - Harmony, 1995 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 107)
  - Harmony, 1996 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 108)
  - Harmony, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 109)
  - Harmony, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 110)
  - Hope of Cure, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 111)
  - The House of Prayer Newsletter, Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 112)
  - Houston Peace News, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 113)
  - Human Kindness Foundation, Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 114)
  - Human Kindness Foundation - newsletters, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 115)
  - Human Kindness Foundation - newsletters, 1995 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 116)
  - Human Kindness Foundation - newsletters, 1995 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 117)
  - Human Kindness Foundation - newsletters, 1996 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 118)
  - Human Kindness Foundation - newsletters, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 119)
  - Humanitas - newsletters, 1992 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 120)
  - I Oppose the Death Penalty: Don't Kill For Me - Button, Undated (Oversize 5, Item 11)
  - Illinois Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1992; 1994-1995; Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 121)
  - Indiana Citizens to Abolish Capital Punishment, 1998; Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 122)
  - Indiana Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1989; 1991-1992 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 123)
  - Indiana Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty - conference packet, 1989 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 124)
  - Indianapolis Coalition to Abolish Capital Punishment, 1998; Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 125)
  - Indianapolis Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 126)
  - Indianapolis Peach and Justice, 1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 127)
  - Innocent on Death Row: The Ten Year Story of Rolando Cruz - Poster, Undated (Flat-file 4)
  - Intercommunity Justice and Peace Centers -Issues, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 128)
  - Interfaith Pilgrimage for Peace and Life, 1994 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 129)
  - International Federation of Action by Christians for the Abolition of Torture, 1995; Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 130)
  - International Federation of Action by Christians for the Abolition of Torture - The Tortured, Torturers, and Christian Hope, 1990 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 131)
  - International Forgiveness Institute, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 132)
  - Iowa's Democratoc Left Newsletter -The Prairie Progressive, 1992 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 133)
  - Iowans Against the Death Penalty, 1992-1995; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 134)
  - Jubilee Partners, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (6-General Activism), Folder 135)
  - Justice Report, 1992-1997; Undated (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 1)
  - Kansas Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1991; 1996; Undated (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 2)
  - La Voz, 1993 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 3)
  - The Lamp of Hope Project, 1993-1995; 1997; Undated (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 4)
  - Liberarsi dalla necessita del carcere, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 5)
  - Life Advocate, 1993 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 6)
  - LifeLines, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 7)
  - LifeLines - The Wing of Friendship, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 8)
  - Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 9)
  - Lighting the Torch of Conscience - packet, 1990 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 10)
  - Lionheart Foundation, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 11)
  - Lionheart Foundation, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 12)
  - Lionheart Foundation, Undated (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 13)
  - The Lionheart Foundation Newsletter, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 14)
  - Live and Let Live, 1993 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 15)
  - Lousiana Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty -The Pilgrimage, 1997 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 16)
  - Lousiana Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty -The Pilgrimage, 1998 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 17)
  - Lousiana Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty -The Pilgrimage, 1998 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 18)
  - Love over Vengeance, Undated (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 19)
  - Massachusetts Citizens Against the Death Penalty, 1990; Undated (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 20)
  - The Mediator, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 21)
  - Mennonite Central Committee, 1992-1995; Undated (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 22)
  - Mid - Missouri Fellowship for Reconciliation, Undated (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 23)
  - Mid - Missouri Fellowship for Reconciliation -FOR News, 1998 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 24)
  - Mid - Missouri Fellowship for Reconciliation -FOR News, 1998 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 25)
  - Mid - Missouri Fellowship for Reconciliation -FOR News, 1998 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 26)
  - Mid - Missouri Fellowship for Reconciliation -FOR News, 1999 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 27)
  - Millions to Kill, Pennies to Heal Banner, Undated (Oversize 5, Item 13)
  - Minnesota Advocates for Human Rights, 1993; 1995-1997 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 28)
  - Minnesota Advocates for Human Rights -Human Rights Observer, 1996 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 29)
  - Minnesota Advocates for Human Rights -Human Rights Observer, 1996 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 30)
  - Minnesota Advocates for Human Rights -Human Rights Observer, 1997 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 31)
  - Minnesota Advocates for Human Rights -Human Rights Observer, 1999 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 32)
  - Missions and Mental Health Conference -Forgiveness in Healing Wounded Servants, 1992 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 33)
  - NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund, 1990; 1992-1994; 1996; Undated (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 34)
  - NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund - Death Row, U.S.A., 1991-1994; 1997 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 35)
  - Napier Network, 1993-1995; 1993/1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 36)
  - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Oppression -Organizer, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 37)
  - National Campaign to Stop Control Unit Prisons, 1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 38)
  - National Commission on Capital Punishment, Undated (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 39)
  - National Conference on Forgiveness, 1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 40)
  - National Conference on Forgiveness in Clinical Practice, 1996 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 41)
  - National Conference on Forgiveness Packet, 1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 42)
  - National Conference on Wrongful Convictions and the Death Penalty, 1998 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 43)
  - National CURE, 1991 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 44)
  - National CURE, 1992 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 45)
  - National CURE, 1993 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 46)
  - National CURE, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 47)
  - National CURE, 1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 48)
  - National CURE, 1996 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 49)
  - National CURE, 1997 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 50)
  - National CURE, 1998-2000; Undated (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 51)
  - National Lawyers Guild - Prison Law Project, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 52)
  - National Lawyers Guild - Prison Law Project, 1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 53)
  - National Lawyers Guild - Prison Law Project, 1996 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 54)
  - National Lawyers Guild - Prison Law Project, 1997 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 55)
  - National Lawyers Guild - Prison Law Project, 1997 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 56)
  - National Organizing Committee, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 57)
  - National Organizing Committee -People's Tribune, 1993 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 58)
  - National Organizing Committee -People's Tribune, 1993 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 59)
  - National Organizing Committee -People's Tribune, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 60)
  - National Organizing Committee -People's Tribune, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 61)
  - National Organizing Committee -People's Tribune, 1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 62)
  - National Organizing Committee -People's Tribune, 1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 63)
  - National Organizing Committee -Tribuno del Pueblo, 1993 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 64)
  - Nebraska Coalition for Victims of Crimes - newsletters, 1992-1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 65)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty, 1991-1996; Undated (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 66)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 67)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 68)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 69)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 70)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 71)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1996 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 72)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1996 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 73)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1996 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 74)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1996 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 75)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1996 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 76)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1997 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 77)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1998 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 78)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1998 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 79)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1998 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 80)
  - New Hope House, 1990; Undated (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 81)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1989 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 82)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1990 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 83)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1991 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 84)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1991 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 85)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1991 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 86)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1992 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 87)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1992 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 88)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1992 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 89)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1992 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 90)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1992 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 91)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1993 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 92)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1993 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 93)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1993 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 94)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1993 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 95)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 96)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 97)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 98)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 99)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1994 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 100)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 101)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 102)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 103)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1995 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 104)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1996 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 105)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1996 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 106)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1996 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 107)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1996 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 108)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1997 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 109)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1997 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 110)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1997 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 111)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1997 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 112)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1998 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 113)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1998 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 114)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1998 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 115)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1998 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 116)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1999 (Box 3 (6-General Activism), Folder 117)
  - The New Party, 1993 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 1)
  - Northern Indiana Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1996-1998; Undated (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 2)
  - Northwest Indiana Coalition to Abolish Control Unit Prisons, 1996-1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 3)
  - Northwest Indiana Federation of Labor -The Voice, 1992 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 4)
  - Northwest Indiana Steering Committee to Stop Supermaximum Prisons, 1996 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 5)
  - NYS Coalition for Criminal Justice -NYSCCJ Update, 1992 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 6)
  - Odyssey: Creative Alternatives in Criminal Justice, 1992 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 7)
  - Offender Victim Ministries, Inc. -OVM Newsletter, 1991 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 8)
  - Ohio Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 9)
  - Ohioans to Stop Executions -The Stoppit, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 10)
  - Ohioans to Stop Executions -The Stoppit, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 11)
  - Ohioans to Stop Executions -The Stoppit, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 12)
  - Ohioans to Stop Executions -The Stoppit, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 13)
  - The Open Door Community, 1991-1995; Undated (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 14)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1990 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 15)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1991 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 16)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1991 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 17)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1991 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 18)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1992 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 19)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1993 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 20)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1994 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 21)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1994 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 22)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1994 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 23)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1995 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 24)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1996 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 25)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1996 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 26)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1996 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 27)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1996 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 28)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 29)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 30)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 31)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 32)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 33)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1999 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 34)
  - Oregon Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 35)
  - Oregon Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1996-1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 36)
  - Oregon Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 37)
  - Oregon Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 38)
  - Oregon Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 39)
  - Parents of Murdered Children, 1991; 1994 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 40)
  - Partison Defense Committee, 1990; Undated (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 41)
  - PAX Christie, 1993; 1995-1997; Undated (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 42)
  - PAX Christie -Catholic Peace Voice, 1995 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 43)
  - PAX Christie -Catholic Peace Voice, 1995 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 44)